croatiaairlines.com 2019-05-31

# Croatia Airlines - Privacy statement

Croatia Airlines is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Croatia Airlines Web site and governs data collection and usage. 

Please read this text in its entirety in order to help us protect your privacy and to understand what information we collect from you and how we use it. You can send all your questions regarding data confidentiality to the email address below: [gdpr@croatiaairlines.hr](mailto:gdpr@croatiaairlines.hr)

## Collection of your Personal Information

Croatia Airlines collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Croatia Airlines also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Croatia Airlines. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Croatia Airlines for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Croatia Airlines Web site.

Croatia Airlines encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Croatia Airlines so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Croatia Airlines is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Croatia Airlines  Web sites.

## Use of your Personal Information

Croatia Airlines collects and uses your personal information to operate the Croatia Airlines Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Croatia Airlines also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Croatia Airlines and its affiliates. Croatia Airlines may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Croatia Airlines does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Croatia Airlinesmay, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Croatia Airlines may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Croatia Airlines, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Croatia Airlines does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Croatia Airlines EN keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Croatia Airlines, in order to determine what Croatia Airlines services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Croatia Airlines EN to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Croatia Airlines Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Croatia Airlines or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Croatia Airlines EN; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Croatia Airlines, or the public.

## Use of Cookies

The Croatia Airlines Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Croatia Airlines pages, or register with Croatia Airlines site or services, a cookie helps Croatia Airlines to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Croatia Airlines Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Croatia Airlines features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Croatia Airlines services or Web sites you visit.

## Security of your Personal Information

Croatia Airlines secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Croatia Airlines secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Your personal data is kept on the server which may be accessed only by authorised persons and service providers. 

Other websites which may be accessed through our website have their own statements regarding privacy and data collection as well as website use and publishing, and Croatia Airlines d.d. shall not be held liable for third-party data collection and processing methods and terms and conditions.

## Changes to this Statement

Croatia Airlines will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Croatia Airlines encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Croatia Airlines is protecting your information.

## Contact Information

Croatia Airlines welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Croatia Airlines has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Croatia Airlines at [webmaster@croatiaairlines.hr](mailto:webmaster@croatiaairlines.hr). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
